我自娱自乐，荣辱不惊
事了拂衣去，深藏功名
以梦为码，仗键横行
痛快Hacking，激情Coding
有朋自远方来，不亦乐乎
志同道合，吾道不孤
面对屏幕，遥想当初
少年志气，咬牙不服输
Open code, open world
Open code makes
an open world
Open code and open source
Collaboration
for a better world
我呼朋唤友，畅快悠游
黑客的天性，就爱自由
软件的free不是免费啤酒
是进步创新的自由！
对酒当歌，人生几何？
志同道合，我们难分难舍
社区团聚，尽情分享
开源之夜，欢声笑语多
Just for fun, we inspire
Fork the project
and make it right
Submit the changes
and patch the night
Talk is cheap
let's code in light
无论 Richard Stallman
还是 Linus Torvalds
带领着我们，自由与开源
我们心里发着光！
Open code, open world
Open code makes
an open world
Open code and open source
Collaboration
for a better world
Open code, open world
Open code makes
an open world
Open code and open source
Collaboration
for a better world
Just for fun, we inspire
Fork the project
and make it right
Submit the changes
and patch the night
Talk is cheap
let's code in light
OPEN CODE
OPEN WORLD
OPEN CODE MAKES
AN OPEN WORLD
OPEN CODE
OPEN SOURCE
COLLABORATION
FOR A BETTER WORLD
开源人之歌
献给
天下开源人